{
    "Science-Questions": [
        {
            "QID": "1",
            "question": "What is the biggest planet in our solar system?",
            "answer-1": "Earth",
            "answer-2": "Jupiter",
            "answer-3": "Mars",
            "answer-4": "Neptune",
            "correct": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
            "QID": "2",
            "question": "The fear of what animal is arachnophobia?",
            "answer-1": "Spiders",
            "answer-2": "Cows",
            "answer-3": "Owls",
            "answer-4": "Whales",
            "correct": "Spiders"
        },
        {
            "QID": "3",
            "question": "What famous scientist was awarded the 1921 Nobel Prize in Physics for his work on theoretical physics?",
            "answer-1": "George Beadle",
            "answer-2": "Linus Pauling",
            "answer-3": "Isaac Newton",
            "answer-4": "Albert Einstein",
            "correct": "Albert Einstein"
        },
        {
            "QID": "4",
            "question": "Pure water has a PH of about",
            "answer-1": "7.0",
            "answer-2": "6.0",
            "answer-3": "9.0",
            "answer-4": "4.0",
            "correct": "7.0"
        },
        {
            "QID": "5",
            "question": "What is the highest mountian on Earth?",
            "answer-1": "Mount Fuji",
            "answer-2": "Mount Sanford",
            "answer-3": "Mount Everest",
            "answer-4": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
            "correct": "Mount Everest"
        },
        {
            "QID": "6",
            "question": "What is the name of the long appendage that hangs off an elephants face?",
            "answer-1": "Fin",
            "answer-2": "Trunk",
            "answer-3": "Giblet",
            "answer-4": "Tail",
            "correct": "Trunk"
        },
        {
            "QID": "7",
            "question": "Where can flamingos NOT be found?",
            "answer-1": "Americas",
            "answer-2": "Africa",
            "answer-3": "Middle East",
            "answer-4": "Northern Europe",
            "correct": "Northern Europe"
        },
        {
            "QID": "8",
            "question": "What compound makes plants green?",
            "answer-1": "Chlorophyll",
            "answer-2": "Salt",
            "answer-3": "Potasium",
            "answer-4": "Nitrogen",
            "correct": "Chlorophyll"
        },
        {
            "QID": "9",
            "question": "What is the name of the star closest to earth besides the sun?",
            "answer-1": "Barnard's Star",
            "answer-2": "Siruis",
            "answer-3": "Epsilon Indi",
            "answer-4": "Alpha Centauri",
            "correct": "Alpha Centauri"
        },
        {
            "QID": "10",
            "question": "Molten rock that comes out of a volcano is known as what?",
            "answer-1": "Magma",
            "answer-2": "Lava",
            "answer-3": "Sedimentary",
            "answer-4": "Metamorphic",
            "correct": "Lava"
        }
    ]
}